<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="food_drink_business_name">
        <item>Atlantis Steakhouse</item>
        <item>Sky Terrace Sushi Bar</item>
        <item>The Grand Buffet</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_phone_number">
        <item>7758244430</item>
        <item>7758244434</item>
        <item>7757892000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_address">
        <item>3800 South Virginia Street, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>3800 South Virginia Street, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>2500 East 2nd Street, Reno, NV 89502</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_address_geo">
        <item>39.4887853,-119.7939481</item>
        <item>39.4887853,-119.7939481</item>
        <item>39.523354,-119.7813853</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_website">
        <item>https://www.atlantiscasino.com/reno-restaurants/atlantis-seafood-steak-house/</item>
        <item>https://www.atlantiscasino.com/reno-restaurants/atlantis-sushi-bar</item>
        <item>https://www.grandsierraresort.com/dining-and-lounges/the-grand-buffet</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_description">
        <item>Atlantis Steakhouse is proud to be the
            recipient of the AAA Four Diamond award. Only 2.6% of the 29,000 restaurants across the
            United States, Canada, Mexico and the Caribbean rated by AAA receive this prestigious
            designation.
            \n\nRecently voted Best Overall Steakhouse in the Reno – Tahoe area by OpenTable diners.
            \n\nCapturing the cosmopolitan essence of Chicago to San Francisco, the Atlantis Steakhouse
            is impeccably styled with a design that melds contemporary elegance with classic comfort.
            \n\nAtlantis proudly serves Allen Brothers of Chicago meats, the nation’s finest steaks.
            These wet-aged USDA prime cuts are the ultimate grade of beef, chosen for their superb
            quality, marbling and flavor. Experience the art of traditional Steakhouse table side dining,
            unsurpassed service and unmatched attention to detail. Glowing honey onyx exudes warmth and
            the plush dining settees create a dining ambiance second to none. Classic cocktails,
            metropolitan martinis and over 336 selections of wine complete your experience. Exclusive
            private dining for groups of 15 to 50 may be arranged.</item>
        <item>Enjoy delicious all-you-care-to-eat sushi on the scenic Sky Terrace.
            \n\nFeaturing a selection of over 50 types of nigiri and maki sushi, our Sushi Bar offers
            an entertaining and unique dining experience. Complement your choices with any one of
            eight brands of premium sake, plum wines or an assortment of domestic and imported beers.
            \n\nWhether it\'s lunch or dinner, our Sushi Bar offers the perfect ambiance for any kind
            of occasion. Located adjacent to the Oyster Bar on the non-smoking, scenic Sky Terrace.</item>
        <item>" "</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="food_drink_business_image">
        <item>@drawable/atlantis_logo_color</item>
        <item>@drawable/atlantis_logo_color</item>
        <item>@drawable/atlantis_logo_color</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>