<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="food_drink_business_name">
        <item>Atlantis Steakhouse</item>
        <item>Sky Terrace Sushi Bar</item>
        <item>The Grand Buffet</item>
        <item>Silver Peak on the River</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_phone_number">
        <item>7758244430</item>
        <item>7758244434</item>
        <item>7757892000</item>
        <item>7752843300</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_address">
        <item>3800 South Virginia Street, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>3800 South Virginia Street, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>2500 East 2nd Street, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>135 North Sierra Street, Reno, NV 89501</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_address_geo">
        <item>39.4887853,-119.7939481</item>
        <item>39.4887853,-119.7939481</item>
        <item>39.523354,-119.7813853</item>
        <item>39.5257098,-119.8146367</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_drink_business_website">
        <item>https://www.atlantiscasino.com/reno-restaurants/atlantis-seafood-steak-house/</item>
        <item>https://www.atlantiscasino.com/reno-restaurants/atlantis-sushi-bar</item>
        <item>https://www.grandsierraresort.com/dining-and-lounges/the-grand-buffet</item>
        <item>http://www.silverpeakbrewery.com/</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="food_drink_business_image">
        <item>@drawable/atlantis_logo_color</item>
        <item>@drawable/atlantis_logo_color</item>
        <item>@drawable/grand_sierra_resort_logo_black</item>
        <item>@drawable/silver_peak_logo</item>
    </integer-array>
    <!--*****************************************************************************************-->
    <string-array name="shopping_business_name">
        <item>Meadowood Mall</item>
        <item>MidTown District</item>
        <item>Outlets at Sparks</item>
        <item>RiverWalk District</item>
        <item>The Summit</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shopping_business_phone_number">
        <item>7758278450</item>
        <item>NA</item>
        <item>7753583800</item>
        <item>7758259255</item>
        <item>7758537800</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shopping_business_address">
        <item>5000 Meadowood Mall Cir, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>805 South Virginia St, Box 210, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>1310 Scheels Drive, Sparks NV 89434</item>
        <item>P.O. Box 1606, Reno, NV 89505</item>
        <item>13925 S Virginia St, Suite 212, Reno, NV 89511</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shopping_business_address_geo">
        <item>39.473876,-119.7828682</item>
        <item>39.5177447,-119.8090539</item>
        <item>39.5313132,-119.7210068</item>
        <item>39.5257701,-119.8154218</item>
        <item>39.4039208,-119.7504795</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shopping_business_website">
        <item>http://www.simon.com/mall/meadowood-mall</item>
        <item>http://www.renomidtowndistrict.com/shopping-index/#shopping-main</item>
        <item>http://www.outletsatsparks.com/</item>
        <item>http://renoriver.org/</item>
        <item>http://thesummitreno.com/</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shopping_business_image">
        <item>@drawable/meadowood_logo</item>
        <item>@drawable/midtown_logo</item>
        <item>@drawable/outlets_logo</item>
        <item>@drawable/riverwalk_logo</item>
        <item>@drawable/summit_logo</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--*****************************************************************************************-->
    <string-array name="outdoor_name">
        <item>Biking</item>
        <item>Hiking</item>
        <item>Parks</item>
        <item>Golf</item>
        <item>Horseback Riding</item>
        <item>Sports</item>
        <item>Fishing</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="outdoor_images">
        <item>@drawable/biking</item>
        <item>@drawable/hiking</item>
        <item>@drawable/parks</item>
        <item>@drawable/golf</item>
        <item>@drawable/horseback_riding</item>
        <item>@drawable/sports</item>
        <item>@drawable/fishing</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="outdoor_description">
        <item>Reno Tahoe is the ideal place for cycling and mountain biking enthusiasts!
        \n\nCITY CYCLING
            \n\nThe city is bike friendly with a series of well-marked, connecting bike lanes that
            rivals or surpasses bike lane route systems in other cities.
            \n\nThe Truckee River has one of the prettiest paths to bike along. The 12-mile Truckee
            River Bike Path runs from west of Chrissie Caughlin Park are eastward along the Truckee
            River through downtown Reno and runs all the way to the very eastern end of the city of
            Sparks.
        \n\nMOUNTAIN BIKING
            \n\nIf you’re looking to get off the beaten path and onto some dirt, there are several
            mountain biking trails, bikeways and parks available to get your adrenaline rushing.
            The Peavine Trail is located just north of downtown and offers some insane views of the
            city and terrain suitable for all levels. Make sure you bring plenty of water because
            shade is limited on this barren but exhilarating ride. The Tahoe Rim Trail and Flume
            Trail are both home to world-class mountain biking with everything from epic views on a
            mellow singletrack to burly climbs and exhilarating descents.
            \n\nReno Tahoe is also close to top-notch mountain bike parks. During the summer months,
            ski resorts Northstar and Kirkwood offer lift-accessed trails from beginner to advanced.
        </item>

        <item>Reno and Tahoe hiking trails incorporate some of the most beautiful scenery in all of
            northern Nevada with one of the purest forms of exercise.
            \n\nWith so much terrain, the hardest part is picking which trail to venture onto today.
            Located within the city limits of Reno, you can take the popular Hunter Creek Trail
            which will take you to a hidden waterfall. Other popular urban hikes include Huffaker
            Hills, which will reward you with great views of the city from atop the hills of South
            Reno or the hike to the ‘N’ located in Rancho San Rafael Regional Park.
            \n\nAnother popular hiking area is Galena Creek Regional Park, located in South Reno at
            the base of Mount Rose Highway. Here you can find hikes ranging from under 2 miles, to
            the epic 9.2 mile Jones Whites Creek Loop.
            \n\nAnd then you have Lake Tahoe. The Mount Rose Trail is a grueling 9.5 mile round-trip
            hike with 1,930 ft. in elevation gain, taking you to the peak of Mount Rose at 10,776
            ft. From the summit, you can see much of the Lake Tahoe Basin and the Truckee Meadows.
            Take advantage of the rocky wind shelter up top while you savor your well-deserved
            picnic lunch before making the climb down.  Other popular Tahoe hikes include the Tunnel
            Creek Trail to Monkey Rock and Spooner Lake to Marlette Lake. If backpacking is more
            your style, you’re in the right place. Check out the Tahoe Rim Trail or Desolation
            Wilderness for trail maps and permit guides
        </item>

        <item>Discover Reno Tahoe’s incredible outdoors and nature. With 300 days of sunshine there
            is no reason to stay indoors. Our region is full of beautiful natural landscapes,
            vibrant wildlife and several parks the kiddos can play in!
            \n\nIf you’re not in the mood to hike the trails of Lake Tahoe, take a stroll through
            Reno’s Riverwalk district or participate in any other recreational activity Reno Tahoe
            has to offer, we have parks in our area that will still allow you to enjoy our blue
            skies, the landscapes of the Sierra Nevada and breath taking sunsets. Don’t miss our on
            what our beautiful region has to offer by staying indoors.
            \n\nRancho San Rafael, in Reno is a neighboring park with a great, scenic view of The
            Biggest Little City. Don’t be fooled by the only areas you can see driving past it.
            There is plenty to explore, a play area for the kids with slides and jungle gym, a
            wetland habitat and a designated area for our furry friends to play in!
            \n\nLake Tahoe Nevada State Park is a major attraction to all lake go-ers. It is popular
            for picnicking, hiking, mountain biking, catch-and-release fishing and cross-county
            skiing.
            \n\nKings Beach, in North Lake Tahoe, offers a playground for the kids. Walk towards the
            water and you will discover the beach that offers an unbelievable view of the
            surrounding mountains and lake.
            \n\nThe Sparks Marina is located off I-80 east to McCarran Blvd. It has two beaches,
            picnic areas, a fishing pier, a 2-mile walking path, volleyball courts, playgrounds
            and any other park amenity you will need on a day out at the park. If you stay through
            the evening you will experience a beautiful Reno Tahoe sunset with capturing clouds
            and pretty city lights.
            \n\nGalena Creek Park is popular year-round. In the summer, enjoy hiking in the Sierra
            along Galena, Jones and White’s Creeks; in the winter, visit the park for sledding and
            cross-country skiing. Galena Creek flows through the park creating separate north and
            south portions of the park. Campfire programs, ranger-led hikes, and exhibits in the old
            stone visitor’s center add to the diversity of the park.
            \n\nDavis Creek Regional Park offers picnic facilities, and group camping site are
            available by reservation. An equestrian trailhead provides access to the Toiyabe
            National Forest. This campground/day use area offers outstanding views of Washoe Lake
            and Slide Mountain. During the coldest months of winter, the pond freezes and makes a
            great ice skating area, which is free to the public. This diverse park is a favorite
            among locals.
        </item>

        <item>You’ll never play a better game of golf than when you’re in Reno Tahoe. It’s science.
            At our altitude, golf balls automatically fly 10 percent farther. Your ball will
            literally slice through our thinner air like a hot knife through butter. And with over
            50 courses within 90 minutes of Reno, there’s a course for every level of play.
            \n\nIn Reno, courses include the state’s oldest links — the Washoe County Golf Course,
            which was established in 1934 – and the newest courses, including ArrowCreek and Red
            Hawk. We’re even home to Montreux Golf Club, home of the PGA stop Barracuda Championship.
            \n\nYou’ll also find courses like Wildcreek, LakeRidge and Wolf Run Golf Club in Reno.
            Carson City, our state capital and just a 30-minute drive south, offers the Divine Nine
            courses, totaling about 70,000 yards of greens and roughs, including Dayton Valley
            Country Club, Empire Ranch, and the Golf Club at Genoa Lakes.
            \n\nLake Tahoe is a 60-minute drive up winding mountains and offers a dozen championship
            courses, including Edgewood Tahoe, where the star-sutdded American Century Championship
            is held in July. Edgewood is rated one of Golf Digest’s top 25 public U.S. golf courses.
            \n\nSo you’d rather be a spectator? Well, Reno Tahoe also has popular events that
            attract visitors, locals and golf professionals each year.
            \n\nTaking place in late July/early August is the Barracuda Championship PGA Tour Golf
            Tournament. This game is played in a unique format, which encourages the players to
            shoot for the pin creating more excitement for spectators. Watch some of the worlds best
            golfers as they compete for a $3.3 million purse and 300 FedExCup points.
            \n\nThe American Century Celebrity Golf Tournament is one of the most anticipated
            golfing events in Reno Tahoe. It has helped raise millions of dollars to help support
            local and national charities and organizations. This tournament hosts chart-topping
            actors, singers and professional sports stars as the compete in a 54-hole modified
            Stableford format while the public gets in on all the action!
        </item>

        <item>Our region offers horseback expeditions year-round. We welcome all levels and types of
            riders and for those who are new to horseback riding there are clinics at most of our
            local equestrian centers. We have hundreds of thousands of acres of public lands begging
            to be explored making the riding opportunities in Reno Tahoe an excellent destination
            for the equine enthusiasts.
            \n\nHere, riders can ride through trails, hidden passages or surrounding alpine. Some
            rider may choose to ride on their own and make their own back. Other riders can hire a
            guide such as Sierra Adventures or Piping Rock Horses and ride the desert wilderness for
            a multi-day trip around the guide’s chosen area. Being at such close proximity to Lake
            Tahoe,  soak up the sun and take a dip in the pristine water and late afternoon begin
            your horseback expedition and watch the cotton candy sky turn into night in Reno. Daily
            itineraries are diverse and endless in Reno Tahoe!
        </item>

        <item>RENO ACES
            \n\nThe Reno Aces are a Minor League Baseball franchise; the team is a member of the
            Pacific Coast League and is the Triple-A affiliate of the Arizona Diamondbacks. Owned by
            SK Baseball, the Aces are a part of the Pacific Conference’s North Division along with
            the Colorado Springs Sky Sox, Salt Lake Bees, and Tacoma Rainiers. Greater Nevada Field,
            a 9,100-capacity venue constructed for the team, opened in Spring 2009 in the heart of
            downtown Reno. The stadium is part of the Freight House District, an exciting year-round
            entertainment complex that offers unparalleled retail, dining and nightlife options.
        \n\nRENO BIGHORNS
            \n\nThe Reno Bighorns are an NBA G League team owned and operated by the Sacramento
            Kings. The team plays at the Reno Events Center in the heart of downtown Reno, from late
            November through early April. Tickets can be purchased online through ticket master or
            at the Silver Legacy Box office.
        \n\nRENO 1868 FC
            \n\nThe Reno 1868 FC is a United Soccer League team affiliated with Major League
            Soccer’s San Jose Earthquakes. The team’s inaugural season is in full effect at Greater
            Nevada Field, located in downtown Reno. The USL regular season spans from March to
            September, with playoff games in October.
        \n\nNEVADA WOLF PACK
            \n\nThe University of Nevada, Reno has a long and storied athletics tradition. Often
            known as UNR within the state, the school goes by the Nevada Wolf Pack for athletics.
            They are a Division I (FBS for football) collegiate program and compete in the Mountain
            West Conference. Visit the University’s Athletic site to learn more about the Wolf Pack.
        </item>

        <item>With so much water around, it’s no wonder Reno Tahoe is a premier fishing destination!
            \n\nPyramid Lake, located on a Paiute Indian Reservation 45 minutes north of Reno, is
            the end point of the Truckee River. Widely acclaimed as North America’s most beautiful
            desert lake, it was the world class fishery that brought Pyramid Lake to fame. You can
            catch Cui-ui which is endemic to the lake or the famous Lohanton Cutthroat. The trout
            have grown to record sizes and attract fisherman from around the world. For more
            information on fishing permits and fishing conditions at the lake, please visit their
            website.
            \n\nFishing the Truckee is another popular spot for anglers. The Truckee River offers
            some of the best water in the west – including a fly-fishing only, catch-and-release
            section – easily accessible from the Interstate 80 corridor through downtown Reno. With
            so many excellent places to fish, we want to link you out to a few resources to help
            aide your decision.
            \n\nReno Fly Shop– A locally owned and operated downtown fishing shop, their website
            will list some local waters and they often release a fishing report.
            \n\nNevada Department of Wildlife– As your go-to source for all hunting, fishing, and
            wildlife in Nevada, this is a great resource to use when looking up permit options and
            regulations or researching both urban ponds or remote and beautiful fishing holes.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nightlife_name">
        <item>EDGE Nightclub</item>
        <item>LEX Nightclub</item>
        <item>Brew Brothers</item>
        <item>Novi Lounge</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nightlife_address">
        <item>2707 South Virginia Street, Reno, NV 89502</item>
        <item>2500 East 2nd Street, Reno, Nevada 89595</item>
        <item>345 North Virginia Street, Reno, NV 89501</item>
        <item>345 North Virginia Street, Reno, NV 89501</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nightlife_address_geo">
        <item>39.4968587,-119.8009559</item>
        <item>39.5232284,-119.7791997</item>
        <item>39.5291693,-119.8146801</item>
        <item>39.5291693,-119.8146801</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nightlife_description">
        <item>Located in the Peppermill Reno, EDGE Nightclub celebrates the art of nightlife by staying true to authentic DJ culture, choreographed dance vignettes, and music and turntablism. Come and see this high energy, award-winning nightclub for yourself.</item>
        <item>An unprecedented nightlife venue, LEX Nightclub, located in the Grand Sierra Resort, is the premier nightclub in northern Nevada. At an impressive 25,000 sq. ft., LEX features three full bars, 33 VIP tables and a bevy of deluxe amenities to create the experience of a lifetime.</item>
        <item>Restaurant by day, nightclub by night, Brew Brothers, located in the Eldorado Resort, offers eight custom microbrews, live music, and DJs nightly. You can enjoy weekly specials such as All-You-Can-Drink Brew Brother’s Beer, and ladies, first drink is free Sunday-Friday before 11 pm.</item>
        <item>The perfect place to get your country on is Novi Lounge located in the Eldorado Resort. Join Novi for All Jacked Up Saturdays and Line Dancing lessons from 9pm-12am. From Country Rock, Pop Rock, Top 40, Blues to Comedy, the excitement and energy of live music is on full display.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nightlife_phone_number">
        <item>18668219996</item>
        <item>7757895399</item>
        <item>7757865700</item>
        <item>7757865700</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nightlife_website">
        <item>https://www.peppermillreno.com/nightlife/edge/</item>
        <item>http://www.lexnightclub.com/</item>
        <item>https://www.eldoradoreno.com/venue/nightclubs/brew-brothers-nightlife</item>
        <item>https://www.eldoradoreno.com/venue/nightclubs/novi</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="nightlife_image">
        <item>@drawable/edge_logo</item>
        <item>@drawable/lex_logo</item>
        <item>@drawable/brew_logo</item>
        <item>@drawable/novi_logo</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>